Our thinking club today
Will organize one
Competition of wits
This contest
Will be based on the eight members' set names
Through a chess game
Stimulates the brain, demonstrates intelligence
Left
Answer correctly
Being in the pressure zone has a purpose
So that's it
The war will surely be won
Get the opportunity to check other people's identities
Now
Half way through
Four players have received effective news
Of these, two people received it
Second test opportunity
The person whose identity I want to check is
Thieu Minh Minh
I want to check
But between Ho Hai Tuyen and Thieu Minh Minh
Choose one person
Who will he choose this time?
This round I want to check
Perhaps between Ho Hai Tuyen and Thieu Minh Minh
Choose one person
Then I'll check out Thieu Minh Minh
I'm so smart
So our second round game is over
The winning group also went to check their identity
Next
In our high school reasoning club
Perfect speaking skills
And think more logically than others
It is also a necessary skill for members
Please arrange members according to new-old formation
To divide the group
Van Thao
Mr. Ho Hai Tuyen
Thieu Minh Minh and Ly Van Kiet formed a group
Our members are below
There will be 4v4 competition
The argument is not logical
After announcing the exam questions
The group representative will draw his/her thesis
Even though the results don't agree with me
You must also respect your own choices
Each topic will be debated freely
After finishing the argument
Will be by thirty fans
Decided via online voting method
And our first topic is
Now, please invite both sides to pick
You, you choose first
You go first
So let me pick the cards
By my side
My side's point of view is:
B: Not being able to wake up is more painful
Not being able to sleep is more painful
What do you think?
No need to think
Surely not being able to wake up would be more painful
Brothers, this verse
Sure
Can't even sleep
So how can I wake up?
First round
Begin
Not being able to sleep is miserable
Why is that?
Because the body will be tired
Because I always stay up late
Then his sleep was not enough
Health is also not good
Will get sick
If you are mentally tired, you cannot sleep
It will be difficult for you to think
You might think about your ex-girlfriend
All kinds of suffering will come rushing back, making not being able to sleep even more painful
Is that right, brothers?
Correct
Can't sleep
Then how can you wake up?
He couldn't sleep
Surely he couldn't get up
Was it very painful when you couldn't bear it?
Because there's still so much you need to do
For example, your work, your love
You cannot do these things
Just thinking about it made me feel so miserable
Because he couldn't get up
So all of his consciousness disappeared
Good
Come on, brother
Counterattack
At first I couldn't sleep
He just couldn't get up
If you think you can't get up
It has been very painful
Then you can't sleep
It is the root cause of suffering
Surely it is the most painful
Why do you find not being able to sleep more painful?
Because he couldn't sleep
What he was worried about was
I won't be able to get up tomorrow
So not being able to get up will be more painful
Normal people work and rest
Definitely sleep time
If he was young, he would open his eyes
Then it's time to close your eyes
For us humanity
It is extremely valuable work
But in this argument
He couldn't even sleep
So how can you have enough?
Concentration
Enough thinking to face the next day
If a person cannot sleep
It may lead to many people being unhappy
If you can't get up
Leading to the whole company being unhappy
The boss's thinking is very good
What else is there?
How many people choose to change their answer?
How many people changed their answers and lined up?
Why
Because he couldn't get up
He couldn't get up
He had to spend money to change his name
But as soon as you use money, you will suffer even more
His savings are not much
Is it true?
You say it
I say this
Can't get up
This type of suffering may change
Maybe, your mother will wake you up
The boss will call you to force you to go to work
So you will wake up
Then there will be no more suffering
Precisely because of their urging
That's why it's even more painful, right?
The reason he couldn't get up
It's because there's no one around you
Like Mr. Trieu Van Trac
Think about Trieu Van Trac next to you
Mr. Ho Hai Tuyen is awake
You'll be like a whale bouncing around
Get up immediately
Not everyone is as happy as you guys
There is teacher Trieu Van Trac by my side
I didn't get that chance
Teacher Trieu Van Trac lulled me to sleep
But can't sleep
Extremely happy
Why happy?
You say it
He thinks so
When you can't sleep
We will be in a state of extreme alertness
We can do a lot
We can exercise ourselves
But it's not the same if you can't get up
We cannot wake up completely
In an unconscious state
Struggle when you can't get up
The time we can't sleep
We can use it to
I said listen
The state when a person cannot get up
Actually, I woke up from my sleep
Extremely painful
No, no suffering
I can't get up
I was half awake and half unconscious
But when I can't sleep, I'm extremely alert
He was in bed
Very painful
Can't sleep, very miserable
Performing right?
We just finished performance class
Can't get up
Mr. Ho Hai Tuyen called me to class
Got to class
Thieu Minh Minh
Pretend
He pretended
This is not wanting to go to school
Come on, leave him alone
Go
Thieu Minh Minh has started recording
Thieu Minh Minh recorded the video
You see why now
Just now I wanted to say I lied
But through practical experience
Finding out that I couldn't get up was really painful
Why
Mr. Ho Hai Tuyen called me to wake up but I didn't wake up
That means I'm late
I was late, I was sad all morning
Because I can't hear
Lectures by teachers
I could be done with my life because
Did not pass the exam
The distance between me and everyone is stretched
It's true that not being able to teach is too painful
Affects the future of life
No, listen to me
He told me why he couldn't wake up
Isn't he suffering?
I tell you
That state of not being able to wake up
It's you who's confused
The alertness of not being able to sleep
Too complicated
Let me tell an experience of my own
Because I entered Ngao Khuyen in the same dorm room
The feeling of not being able to wake up in the morning is too uncomfortable
Because I didn't get enough sleep
I still hear Ngao Khuyen grinding his teeth
Grinding loudly
Every time he wakes me up
Then I got extremely upset
Extremely painful
The last thirty seconds
This is the last chance for each team to show off
Brothers, come on
Sleep
Not being able to sleep is very uncomfortable
Now me
Really want to sleep
Too painful
I think you're not awake yet
Haven't woken up yet
Is it true?
Add a little value
In the classic "Brother who overcomes all obstacles".
In this program
everyone desperately wants to talk
There could be more contributions
But we practice often
At two thirty in the morning
That can't sleep
Then everyone
Depart at eight thirty the next morning
You also have to put on makeup before going
So I can be like
It's not yet seven o'clock
My ears have started
Someone is getting their hair done
But it feels like I can't wake up
It was the most painful time
Other than that, this show is all fun
Thank you in advance, both groups
Acted out a fierce response
Also invite thirty interested spectators to prepare
Please vote
Extremely good
Mr. Ho Hai Tuyen is right
You're so right
Let's start counting
Answer: A or B, which one has more?
In the first round of argument
The group that couldn't get up won
Of course, not being able to sleep is also very painful
Is it true?
Let's talk now
Okay, next
We go in immediately
Second round of argument
Freedom to argue
Our second argument is:
Then it must be said
So not sure
Now, let's see the lottery results
Let's see how it turns out
Please pick up
We chose B: Shouldn't say
Then it is definitely impossible to say
There are a few sentences that can be said, right?
Should definitely say
Circle of free argument
Now begins
I feel like I should say some useless words
Because I am inherently one
People who talk nonsense
Correct
Continue
From the beginning until now
I said a lot of nonsense
Even though he didn't contribute anything to the program
I know
But I feel like I got the audience's laughter back
So I feel
Meaningless words are the joy of life
If I could change their laughter
Does it count as a meaningless sentence?
Besides, you've said too many meaningless words
Not only are you wasting your time
It also wastes the opponent's and everyone's time
Don't say meaningless words
Thieu Minh Minh shouldn't talk anymore now
You also agreed with me
Meaningless words should not be said
Is it true?
After him
Say this again
"God" of logic
You should definitely say a lot of extra sentences
Because, if just now
Don't say a lot of meaningless words like they did last time
So how can you win?
So the recent results have proven it
It should definitely be nonsense
Furthermore, there is much more to say
We are all teenagers
Teenagers are not afraid of anything
It's a mistake
Saying meaningless words is a way to make mistakes
But we will also go through this method of talking a lot
Get the most correct path
So it is said that people are not afraid of making mistakes
Certainly a lot to say
Yes, so everyone has the right to speak
In the eyes of others, words are meaningless
That's why we should say meaningless words
But why should we?
Already know a principle
It's a meaningless word that shouldn't be said much
But what to say?
I see in a peaceful society
It will definitely bring together many types of people
Then it doesn't represent either
There are many types of nonsense
You, if this society
There are no people who like to talk nonsense like us
Then it will be impossible to know
The wisdom of a person who does not talk nonsense is like medicine
I see that
These people don't exist
Then society would be very boring
Even though everyone says that
People who talk nonsense are very boring
Even though we're stupid
But being stupid has its own happiness
I see that there is a very important issue
That's who defined the cluster
This nonsense
I see each one
When expressing your opinion
He will not consider his words meaningless
No, I know what I said is nonsense
I repeat a bit
Actually, Ngao Khuyen is in my room
All the days we talked
He thought it was meaningless words
But to me, there are no meaningless sentences
Suddenly it's harmonious again
Okay
Immediately pull a person from the opposing team
Why do we record every time?
It took seven or eight hours
But it was cut to only one hour
Because there are too many people talking nonsense
Yes, it's because there are so many meaningless sentences
So finally
I just had to cut a lot of unique parts
All nonsense words have been cut out
In between, there are only useful words left
If you don't talk nonsense often
You wouldn't know it
Good
Both sides proceed on their own
Final round of arguments
Meaningless words actually in many cases
If everyone agrees
But if everyone agrees
It can increase the affection between people
So words are meaningless
It is a means of connection between people
It is an indispensable "bridge".
If you think so
This person is always talking nonsense to you
but you still play with that person
Then there's something wrong with your head
Then I see that my head is very problematic
Furthermore, it's not nonsense
Can become a bridge between people
Connect your heart
This is the correct bridge
Is it true?
Nodding very well
Everyone watched, the other person had nodded
I think Thieu Minh Minh is right
Very suitable to join my company
Come on, register
Mr. Ho Hai Tuyen, choose him
Signed it
This round of arguments ends here
Now, please invite the audience
love our high school reasoning club
Prepare well
Conduct an important voting round
Please vote
I think we have to win this round
In this round of argument
Proud Dog, Ricky, Hoa Thu, Bo Tap Tinh
Victory has been achieved
End of competition
Once again, congratulations on your victory
Four people will have the right to change their status
Just before the change
Our eight members
Final pairing must be performed
Pairing will directly affect your accumulated points
Finally, one side monopolizes
Or both lose
Or half on each side
Your members
All have had very important effects
So now let's proceed
Final pairing selection
Everyone will write their names
People want to pair up on the board
If you and your opponent
There are each other's names on the board
Then the pairing will be successful
If that
A situation arises where two people choose one person
Then that person will receive the right to choose again
The other person
Through the winning and losing process we just went through
Free choice will be made
They have to change, right?
No, we have to wait until after the grouping is done
Then progress to change
So scary
Correct
This is full of unknowns
That's right
Then I volunteer to choose someone who cannot change
That's for sure
Okay, everyone
Please write your name on the board
The person you want to pair with
Full of big variables
Four
Ba
Two
One
Now we will announce it to everyone
Name of the last pairing person
Successful pairing
We congratulate
Ho Hai Tuyen and Van Thao
Successful pairing
This is a bit evil
Very scary
My head is starting to hurt
Based on the situation on stage
The people who choose Thieu Minh Minh are
Bo Tap Tinh and Ricky
Now it will be left to Thieu Minh Minh to choose again
Surely they all checked my identity
That's not sure either
Just now he went twice
Ricky
Volunteer to hug them and dance together
Nor do I want others to benefit
No, they must have guessed what I am
Two people from the other side
Bo Tap Tinh and Ricky
Everyone has the right to change their identity
After winning
Can I ask something?
Have you two checked on me yet?
I checked
I know what you are
So are you willing to change your identity for him?
I can
Sure
He has been the "villain" many times
It's not that you don't know
I think trust your own feelings
So are you willing to change for him?
I can
Trust your own feelings
Okay
The companion Minh Minh chose was
Ricky
Congratulations on your successful pairing
On the contrary, I feel worried
So next in the remaining four
First up are the three debate round winners
Have priority of choice
Auction items
Arrogant Dog, I say this
It is if among the three of us
But there are two people in a group
Between these two
It's the struggle
Characterized by internal turmoil
No problem
We don't need to think so complicated
For example, three of us, two of us team up
We can be two sacks
two people ten points
But the situation is now
Ly Van Kiet is a drag
So with us
There must be someone fighting with him
Correct
It's the three of us
Two people will get ten points
There is one person who cannot win points
But the other person
You can also choose to give Ly Van Kiet 20 points
If say three people
It's difficult to discuss and choose
Final decision
Then directly rock, paper, scissors
The loser will choose Ly Van Kiet
I listen to God's arrangements
Three two one
I lost, okay
So I choose Ly Van Kiet
Hoa Thu and Ly Van Kiet
Mr. Ngao Khuyen and Bo Tap Tinh were successfully paired
Next we invite you
Four people won the debate round
Take turns entering the private room to make your selection
In the end, will my identity change?
Have you checked on me yet?
Whether checked or not
So let's change it or not
I hope you check the price
I am scissors
But I will change it to bao
Best case scenario is
The two of us get 10 points each
He could also be tricking you
It's time to explain to Ngao Khuyen
So I changed
Brothers, we don't go out to fool people
So I won't go anymore
You really don't understand Bo Tap Tinh
Immediately went to worship Igian to stir people's hearts
The final result is a battle of scissors and bag
Already in my hand
Members of four groups here
Is it possible to get bonus points?
We will announce it to everyone one by one
First start from
The closest team next to me
Team Van Thao and Mr. Hai Tuyen
The identities of the two of them
In turn, Van Thao pulled
What are you?
You too
Is that right?
Yes and next here
Mr. Hai Tuyen
Pull, each person gets 0 points
Burn
Your identity is
You too, right?
What?
You're too obvious, you're going to the next step
That's right
Very good sir
This is a satisfactory answer
All cruel people
Well, here comes next
It's Thieu Minh Minh and Bridge
Change to scissors
First, I would like to announce it to everyone
Thieu Minh Minh's original identity
From start to finish everything is fine
Bridge
Either way, he's fine
Made an incredibly peaceful choice
He changed the word pull to bag
Each person gets 10 points
I would like to ask if you want to change your identity
And I want to change
Even though I'm a drag
In the previous two rounds I also learned
Ngao Khuyen and Minh Minh are both nothing
I can actually win this race
But I think the process
New is the best experience
Therefore
I want to change my identity into a bag
To share points with Minh Minh
That's right, because Bridge originally had the last name Bao
Peace
Level
Who doesn't want to join Bridge's team?
Yes, the next one is announced
The moment that touches people's hearts has come
Proud Dog and Bo Tap Tinh
In the recent process
Mr. Ngao Khuyen regarding his identity
Didn't change anything
I would like to ask if you want to change your identity
I really want to trust people
Little Tinh Tinh (Bo Tap Tinh) he won't lie to me
He just told me how much he is
And I am also a bag
So I don't change
Bo Tap Tinh has changed his identity
He can trick you
Time to teach you a lesson
I really don't understand Bo Tap Tinh at all
Bo Tap Tinh's word "pull" has changed to "bag".
Each person gets 10 points
Because right from the beginning
What we don't think about is
Van Thao and Mr. Hai Tuyen successfully teamed up
And Minh Minh with our Bridge
So we
The best result is me and Mr. Ngao Khuyen
Each person gets 10 points
There must be one person who doesn't get points
That person is Hoa Thu
We decided with rock, paper, scissors
Mr. Hoa Thu will definitely change
The fate is broken
Or he will maintain his identity as a drag queen
Then with Ly Van Kiet
Crab
Both of them got no points
So I will change my scissors to bags
Don't look at the wrong person
Sure
Peace
But if the person he chooses is you
So I'm not sure yet
Next is Van Kiet, who cannot make a choice
And Mr. Hoa Thu, who can make a choice
What did you choose?
I guess
Mr. Hoa Thu
How much?
Van Kiet
It's scissors
Win 20 points
Actually it's like this
Now I know
Ly Van Kiet is a drag
So whether I choose to pull or cover
Then I don't have points either
If I don't get points anyway
So why not help others do good things?
So my identity as a bag no longer needs to be changed to scissors
So just continue to maintain your status
There is a prerequisite that is
Mr. Hoa Thu knew Van Kiet's identity
That's right, he knows I'm in drag
The beauty of a gentleman, Mr. Hoa Thu
So what is our relationship?
You two
No, I just met my idol
Next this will be
Our second team building category
It is
The most important item of this reasoning club
Werewolf game
By myself
Even though he's a chicken, he's addicted to playing around
I also really want to play
So in the next episode
Please ask for help from club member Thieu Minh Minh
Take on the role of host of this werewolf game
And I will replace Thieu Minh Minh
To be with everyone
Join this werewolf performance
This game includes 3 werewolves
Three "gods" and two villagers
Werewolves can attack 1 person every night
You can confess during the day, until it gets dark
"Divine"
Including prophets, wizards and forbidden elders
The prophet can check a person's identity every night
The witch has a bottle of antidote and a bottle of poison
You cannot use both drugs at the same time at the same time
You can only save yourself on the first night
The elder who prohibits speaking every night can designate one person not to speak
Player is banned from speaking
Can only communicate through body language
This werewolf game applies the rule of extermination
Werewolves kill all "gods" or all the people
Then the wolf will win
The three werewolves each get 10 points
The good guys point out all the werewolves
Then the good side will win
Each player on the good side gets 10 points
Please confirm your identity card
It's dark, please close your eyes
Invite the werewolf to open his eyes
Please ask the werewolves to confirm each other's identities
Invite the werewolf to confirm
Who is the object that people want to attack?
Werewolf please close your eyes
Prophet please open your eyes
Please select the object you want to check
His identity is
Prophet please close your eyes
Witch, please open your eyes
The person who "died" last night was
You have an antidote
Do you want to save that person?
You have a potion of poison
Who do you want to poison?
Witch, please close your eyes
The elder said, please open your eyes
Please select the subject you want to ban
Please, the forbidden elder, please close your eyes
It's morning
The background music sounds so good
That's good
It feels terrible
Last night was a peaceful night
What does peaceful night mean?
No one left
Next, I would like to invite number 1 to begin speaking
I am a person with the identity of the people and above the people
What?
He's a good person
Can you speak human language?
I don't understand this specialized term
Get rid of all the jargon
You are a good person
Who knows?
Talk to the game master
I want to listen to the prophet
It's okay to listen to the prophet
Go away
Go
Yes, number 1 has finished speaking
Invite number 2 to speak
Is number 1 a good person or not?
I'm not too sure either
Anyway, just saying a bunch of nonsense has no effect
It doesn't have any effect
I will choose
I am a prophet
And last night I checked number 6
Number 6 is wolf
Therefore
I helped everyone find a wolf
Should be
Today is definitely number 6
Today we eliminated a wolf
On the second day, the witch must definitely poison another person
Otherwise, it is very difficult for good people to win
So it is
The witch informed a little about the situation of saving people
And then we
Guess the remaining two wolves
Player number two has finished speaking
Invite player number 3
But
You have been banned
Prophet number 2
Prophet
Prophet number 2's way of speaking is problematic
Number 2 is the prophet
Like a prophet
Saying nothing is more than talking
The number of people who helped him speak was also quite large
He wants to choose you
Forget it
It's better to do nothing
The performance of player number 3 is very unique
So player number 4
Can speak
He has never played before
Then the three werewolves don't have to
Where's the first round of dealing with you?
Because he didn't understand anything
Keeping him here will make it easier to take advantage of him
Has exploitation value
That's right
That's exactly the perspective of a business person
Boss's mindset
Please number 5
Anyway, when I remember
In our old days
First time playing this game
It's called "It's dark, close your eyes"
That's right
Maybe ten years ago
And he only played 3 times
I don't understand anything either
It's come today
Anyway, you are
Tieu Bach
Really don't know anything
Yes
Although Mr. Bach Cu Cuong did not come to this episode
But he has already arrived
I am Bach Cu Cuong
Player number 6 can speak
I want to ask number 2
He said I was
Werewolf
Then I want to ask
What he said is definitely true
Doubt
This is my first opinion
The second point of view is:
I am a witch
Because when I opened my eyes
I discovered someone had assassinated me
So I saved myself
Via
So that means
Bridge is a witch
I am a prophet
And I checked number 4
Mr. Hai Tuyen is a good person
And Bo Xi Jing and Quach Van Thao
Maybe it's two wolves
It is
I don't understand number 2 choosing the prophet
Why did the third person speak?
This person is definitely a prophet
If not the same thing
So what else could it be?
What else could it be?
And why should I check?
What is Mr. Hai Tuyen for?
Because like this
Because it's dark
When everyone checks their identity
I've been observing for a bit
What do people look like?
It is
At that time I observed two people
After Bridge saw his identity
He knocked on the table once
And then Mr. Hai Tuyen
After seeing my identity
His whole body suddenly became very serious
So I feel like the two of them have potential
A person with a certain identity
And so it goes
Probably Quach Van Thao and Bo Tap Tinh
They are two ferocious wolves, right?
Plus another teammate to support him
So it's today
Let's just eliminate Quach Van Thao
And then
I won't be checking Bo Ji Jing anymore
Because Bo Xi Jing can be fast
Follow the same rhythm
I feel like it's very difficult for him to be a good person
You are a wizard
I see you poisoned Bo Tap Tinh too
That's it
And I will listen to Ly Van Kiet's speech
And then
It's fine to check him or Qi Tu Quan
Because Qi Sijun was the first to speak
Haven't said anything yet
That's it
Actually the first round when both prophets fight each other
I feel like I quite agree with Mr. Hoa Thu
Please vote number 2
And then if number 2 is not a wolf
That means this prophet has a problem
We eliminate him next
What do you see?
Of course I agree
That's right
Yes
All players have finished speaking
So now
We begin the first round of voting
Please announce the cards
We can see
Number 2 gets 5 votes
And the number 6 in front of us has 2 votes
Bridge voted for number 7
Number 2 was eliminated thanks to votes
Please say your last words
It's a bit hard to understand
At this time
I can only be sure that number 3 is a good person
So the wolf is number 6 and number 7
Because I am certainly a prophet
And number 6 is a bad person
He's on the opposite side of me
Number 7 says he is a prophet
Good person
Other good people cannot choose the prophet
If in this situation I am a prophet
Number 6 number 7 is definitely a pair of wolves
So number 6
Go vote for number 7 again
Logically
Then number 6 is definitely a problem
If number 6 is a good person
Then he can't vote for number 7
He must vote for me
Because I'm the one who said he was a wolf
He must get rid of me
Is that so?
Other good people must understand this logic
So in this vision
Now he wants to strengthen his identity
He voted for number 7
Because number 7 is his wolf teammate
Number 6 and number 7 are a pair of wolves
There's one more
I feel like maybe it is
Could be number 1
The statement of number 1 just now is too ambiguous
Everyone can wait and see what he says later
Now I'm doubt number 1
Anyway, by now the situation has been pushed back
It is
Witches now don't need to choose anymore
Who do you think is the bad person?
Then you poison that person
Because now if you jump out
They will know the situation between "gods" and the people
We also have 3 wolves
There are only 2 people and 2 gods left here
Then I will definitely lose
Let's go
I'm leaving, goodbye
Number 2, please enter the observation room
Hey
We've prepared all the snacks for you
It's so pathetic
It's so difficult
No one believes me
Any
It's dark, please close your eyes
Wolf, please open your eyes
Please confirm
Who is the object you want to attack?
Please close your eyes wolf
Prophet, please open your eyes
Please select the person you want to test
That person's identity is
Prophet please close your eyes
Please open your eyes, witch
Qi Sijun
Qi Tu Quan is a wizard
The person who died last night was
You have an antidote
Do you want to save him?
You have a potion of poison
Who do you want to poison?
Witch, please close your eyes
Please, the forbidden elder, please open your eyes
Please select the subject you want to ban
Please, the forbidden elder, please close your eyes
It's morning
Situation last night
Two people "died"
Number 3 and number 6
There are no last words
Please select the subject you want to ban
Who is the object you want to attack?
What do we have to say?
Then let's go to the observation room and talk
Is that Okay
Love already love
No problem
Ok
There is no last moon
Number 3 didn't even have a chance to talk
Do you know who is a witch?
Him
Not you
Qi Sijun
So Qi Tu Quan had to bear it
Is Mr. Hai Tuyen a forbidden elder?
Looks like Ngao Khuyen, right?
Not
Ngao Khuyen is on the same team as us
Being tricked makes me spin around
Look at the people sitting there
Who did everyone slash?
The first night I slashed this guy
You cut yourself
That's right
Qi Tu Quan was deceived
No wonder
So pathetic
Actually, I could vote for you just now
But I'm only worried if I vote for you
That's too obvious
If you don't vote for me, you'll be exposed
Because no one believes he is a prophet
Got it
We start from the number 7 Fire Tree speaking
The situation is simple now
Because yesterday I confirmed number 8 is a good person
Last night Bo Tap Tinh was definitely poisoned
Then they killed the witch number 6 here
Right
And I have confirmed number 4, Mr. Hai Tuyen
And number 8 Ly Van Kiet is a good person
So now the person's identity is unknown
There are only numbers 1 and 5
Then I recommend this round
The elder forbids it
Reveal your identity
Let the werewolves have too much information
Anyway werewolf in the end
Probably between people number 1 and number 5
Mainly listening to Qi Tu Quan and Ao Khuyen
Listen to two people speak
After that, Ly Van Kiet could speak less
Because I'm afraid you'll reveal your identity
In the end, it was the villagers or the elders who forbade it
Done
Prophet
Yes, player number 7 has finished speaking
So please number 8
I feel he is right
It is
Now there's probably only one wolf left here
And we could be wrong again
Wait a little longer and numbers 1 and 5 will come out
Then wait for it to finish
That's right
Okay, player number 8 has finished his thoughts
Now the number 1 player
I am a witch
Then in the first evening
I took rescue medication #6
Initial
When I spoke in round 1, I didn't make it clear
It's because I'm a witch
If I speak in round 1
Then I feel it's too dangerous
So in round 1 I rarely spoke up
Then number 6
In the morning he woke up and said he was a wizard
Saved myself
Then last night I just downgraded the poison to number 6
So I noticed
The possibility that he is a wolf is very high
If so
He is a wolf
Then statement number 2 has been established
So number 6, number 7, these two are fighting each other
So I will
Choose one person from number 7 or number 8
Then I felt number 4 and number 5
Because I don't see any real information
So you can hear everyone speak
Okay, player number 1 has finished speaking
Now player number 4 can speak
I don't understand what number 1 said
Initially he guarded number 6
Then he poisoned number 6
I have never played
I'm here myself
To express my inner feelings a little
No problem
If so
He said he saved himself
Then there is some logic
Try your best
Alright
That's it
No problem
My first time playing
Much worse than you
Don't be afraid
Just speak boldly
Okay
Number 5
Maybe I won't say things
The type of analysis for everyone to hear
The words are so logical
I see the type that talks a lot
I feel like they are not too honest
In front of my eyes, I see that type of person is you
Uncle
Feeling like I want to say a lot
Prove what?
Maybe I'm not making a clear distinction
Who is the real bad person?
Then finally I said that
Brother overcomes all obstacles
Filming is much easier than this program
Are you tired?
Correct
It's a different experience
Okay, now we're underway
Voting for round two
Now see if three good people can agree to elect one person
If you vote wrong, you will lose
Please vote
Player number 1 was voted by 4 people
Player number 7 has 1 vote
Player number 1 is eliminated
I'm gone
Game
Will end
It's over
Okay, welcome to the waiting room
Let's go back together
Mr. Bridge
What's up?
This feeling
Can share a little
I feel
Although initially the situation was turned around a bit
I said I'm a witch
Really
That said, it's pretty good
But then they told me
That I shouldn't go
Vote me
Say number 7
But in my heart I have a little bit
Blench
Now it is discovered that number 7 is acting
Correct
Are deceiving us
Are deceiving everyone
Ngao Khuyen is also acting
I'm not a good person
So I remember this point of his
But it was discovered later
Didn't find any loopholes either
Bo Tap Tinh is a forbidden elder
I'm not, I'm a civilian
Only Mr. Hai Tuyen
Only
Correct
You're not forbidden, right?
I have forbidden words
But it is strictly forbidden to wrong people
Banned him
Ban me again
I see the first round
He said he committed suicide
I said the number 6 indicates identity
Otherwise he will definitely die
I thought you said number 6
Yesterday he pulled me out
So he's committing suicide
Then he died
I feel the next round if I'm a good person
Then I will definitely pay attention to him
We don't care who is the prophet
You should check him out first
It's okay, next time I won't be a wolf anymore
Okay
The first round werewolves won
The game goes to round 2
We will add a new identity
That's protection
Every night the security guard will choose one person to protect
But it can't be continuous
Choose 1 person both evenings
If the witch's antidote and the guard's protection
They all fall to 1 person
The second act of Werewolf
Now will begin
Okay, everyone, please look at my ID card
Confirmation completed
It's dark, close your eyes
Invite the werewolf to open his eyes
Invite werewolves
Confirm each other's identity
Invite the werewolf to confirm who was killed
Invite the werewolf to close his eyes
Invite the prophet to open his eyes
Invite the prophet to confirm the subject being tested
His identity is
Invite the prophet to close his eyes
Invite the witch to open her eyes
I pass the dead
You have 1 bottle of antidote
Do you want to save him?
You have a bottle of poison, who do you want to kill?
Invite the witch to close her eyes
Invite the guard to open his eyes
Please select the object you want to protect
Invite the guard to close his eyes
It's morning
Last night, one person died
It's number 3
2 rounds of play without saying anything
Please leave your last words
This time the performance was quite good
We can talk now
Security doesn't protect me, I can understand
Because the first evening the guard usually will
Don't protect anyone
But the witch did not save
I don't really understand either
But it could also be
The witch has a problem with me
Feel like I'm killing myself
What is called a problem?
Resentment and hatred
There may be some problem outside with me
But this time
I'm a civilian
I already said that
The words behind
Actually, I revealed my identity
Good people try their best
It's been hard work, please come to our observation area
I said my last words a while ago, it didn't sound right, I was a little shaky
I should say I am a prophet
Mainly don't think that witches don't save
So it's because of my teammates behind me
Surely a prophet will not be chosen
In fact, it is possible not to commit suicide
If I lose this round, it's all my fault
We begin to speak
Start from the right side of the deceased
Player number 4
What to say?
I don't really understand, I've never played this game before
He claims he's a civilian, right?
Not certain
So assassins can also kill themselves
That's right
So this is it
I think I should still listen to what other people have to say
Especially like last time
Having said that, it was revealed
Tell yourself something, listen a little
Okay, player number 4 is done talking
Now invite player number 5 to speak
I said I wanted to be honest
Just now, I was protecting number 4, Mr. Hai Tuyen
Because I don't have a clue either
I do not know
I feel like someone will die
Surely I have to guess and protect that person
That is my responsibility
I'm a security guard
I'm on the righteous side
I do not know
Last time you were an assassin
Last time I was a wolf
Okay, now player number 6
Bridge spoke
First this time
I am a good person with no status at all
Then the second is
Number three is also likely to be the one chosen
My trick of choosing people and number 7
I have already eliminated it myself
But after listening to his statement, I felt it was quite correct
That's point 2
Then point three
I saw four people before my eyes
There are at least 2 wolves
This is how I feel
As for the others, I currently have no clue
Okay, pass
So I have to reveal my identity
I am one
Villagers
Maybe some people will find it very strange
Why do I still have to talk as a villager?
It's because there are many villagers now
Bo Tap Tinh's identity has two possibilities
One is the villager
Two are werewolves
This game has 2 villagers
So if Bo Tap Tinh is a villager
I am also a villager
Then Bridge cannot be a villager
Right
Enough villagers
So here there is a problem
Now the game has stopped guessing the identity
Turn into
A game that uses special effects
So this time win or not
If Ngao Khuyen said he was a security guard
Then you are extremely important
I said villagers
If Bo Tap Tinh is a villager
Werewolves just kill me
Werewolves will win
So do you need to protect me?
And does the witch need to save me?
Think for yourself
How to cooperate with witches
After all, I'm just an ordinary person
This information only goes here
Then do you want to reveal your identity?
Then see for yourself
Anyway, no one says he is a prophet yet
I passed
Talk too much, don't understand
What?
Okay, player number 8 continues speaking
Actually, I quite trust him
But last game he hurt me
Then just now
Number 6 Bridge said he was a villager
At that time, I was actually a bit surprised
No way, two villagers
So I actually have a good person card
Also a villager
But now I don't know who to trust
Because here there are 4 people who say they are villagers
I'm finished
Player number 8 has finished speaking
Player #1 continues
Number 1 is prophetic
Last night I checked that number 7 is a good person
Finally, this round I can trust you for once
There is a rare time when Mr. Hoa Thu is not a wolf
Now we are in doubt
The Wolf King of Detective Academy - Bo Tap Tinh
It's very likely that he's keeping his wolf identity
Kill yourself and leave
If so
There are 2 more wolves here
I will tomorrow night
Let me see number 6 and number 8
Tomorrow I will test number 6
After that, number 2's identity is still unknown
Listen to number 2 for a moment
Please speak number 2
Number 1 is prophetic so it may be correct
No one objected
Furthermore, check out number 7 is a good person
A "god" has no morals
Just now there were enough people like that
It remains to be seen
So I see
Just now, four people accepted to be residents
Then there are 2 wolves
Why do I feel like number 3 doesn't look like a good person?
It's because last round he didn't say a word and left
I feel like wolves can't be "wolves" like that
Still have to kill him first
He hasn't experienced such a game yet
So I have a feeling that he committed suicide
Correct
Then now I'm pretty skeptical of number 6
I feel like number 6 could be the wolf in this round
Just now number 6 did not mention anyone else
He just said
He feels number 3 is a good person
But number 3 said he was a civilian
I didn't know you were a civilian now
He has not changed his opinion
Because behind him there are numbers 7 and 8
They all say they are civilians
Furthermore now number 7
A good person confirmed by prophecy
Statement of number 8
Actually, I feel like there's no problem
If it were me, I would vote number 6
Then the guard
If not, protect the prophet
He protects the prophet
Then he can check one more person
Then on the second day you can talk to us
If you were a security guard
Because no one accepts it
Okay, everyone has finished speaking
We proceed to the first round of voting
Everyone, look at the voting results here
Number 6 is the majority
So number 6 is eliminated
You can say your last words
I'm that good person
Blame me
Actually killing other people is fine
Mostly I should say that I am a prophet
But I panicked
No problem
We're both out
Unless Mr. Hai Tuyen is in there
Can be resisted
Getting through this stage is difficult
Because of this round, Mr. Hai Tuyen
Will definitely be killed by the prophet
That's right
He couldn't let No. 1 continue to check
Correct
There is 1 bottle of antidote left
Really
That's very difficult
Yes, very difficult
He downed the poison
Closing your eyes can also lower the poison
Correct
Next the game will begin
It's dark, please close your eyes
Invite the werewolf to close his eyes
Confirm who was killed
I said villagers
If Bo Tap Tinh is a villager
Then just the werewolf kills me
Werewolves will win
Invite the werewolf to close his eyes
Invite the prophet to open his eyes
Please select the person who wants to check their identity
That person's identity is
Invite the prophet to close his eyes
Invite the witch to open her eyes
It was that person who died last night
I have a bottle of antidote
Do you want to save that person?
I have a bottle of poison, I want to poison someone
Invite the witch to close her eyes
Invite the guard to open his eyes
Please select the object you want to protect
If not, protect the prophet
You are a security guard, so you are very important
Werewolves just kill me
Werewolves will win
So do you need to protect me?
Invite the guard to close his eyes
It's morning
Yesterday was a peaceful night
So please speak, starting with player number 1
Thank you to someone who protected or rescued me
Then I was a prophet
I already checked number 8
Good person
Number 2 from the previous statement
Be a good person
Now among number 4 and number 5 there is 1 person who is a wolf
Choose 1 person out of the 2 of them
Now, number two
Please
So I said it too
I feel the situation is very clear
I am a witch
Afterward
Number 1, number 2, number 7, number 8 are good people
Number 5 said he was a security guard
I see if the two of them don't talk
So basically you are a protector
Unless number 4 says
Wait a moment, the security guard will say it better than you
Listen to number 4 speak
I don't understand why numbers 4 and 5
But we are anyway
I felt like number 1 was saying number 7 earlier
In especially safe situations
I remember voting once
Number 5 votes for number 7
We proceed to the first round of voting
So if you and I
Then of course you are a wolf
He already elected you
Such vague perception
I have finished speaking
Player number 4 has finished speaking
Player number 5 can speak
I'm not fooling anyone, I'm a security guard
Yesterday I defended myself
I see three wolves all here
I feel number 1, number 2 and number 7
Extremely similar to a guild
Then just now
When number 2 spoke
He finally said
If I were the security guard
I can defend number 1
Now I see Qi Sijun
Make eye contact with him
I saw that he was guilty
Then finally share a little
I really believe in Bridge
Correct
Normally he gives me the feeling
What he said was true
He was just killed
Confess that I am a good person
End
Thank you for Ngao Khuyen's trust
Our number 7
Can speak now
Number 1, number 2, number 7 are the same number
Because they are all good people
That's it
Number 1 says he is a prophet
No one here argues with him about this
He can only be a prophet
Number 3 is dead
If he were a prophet, would he have said that?
It won't, right?
If he were a prophet, he would say it right away
Furthermore, we have no objections
So he can only be a prophet
It cannot be otherwise
So he is a prophet
Surely I'm a good person, right?
Looks like Bo Tap Tinh and Bridge now
And Mr. Ho Hai Tuyen, must be 3 wolves
At first I still felt strange
Say that the first round of this game should not save people right away
Why do people die?
Then think a bit
The story of not saving Bo Tap Tinh
It could only be Van Thao who did it
So I think it's quite reasonable, right?
And I am a villager
Player number 8 can speak
I myself am validated by others
I trust him very much
Then I felt I should also follow
End of speech
All players have finished speaking
Now proceed to voting
We are so miserable
This round has been overturned
No, we call the entire army destroyed
Is it me or is it number 7?
Okay
Please vote
Let's take a look
Most people vote number 4
Based on voting results
Number 4 was voted out
Game over
Okay, welcome followers
Return
Why commit suicide?
Really, why not?
I lost this round because of me
At first I committed suicide
I misjudged the situation
No
We just don't trust it
I am guilty
Mr. Ho Hai Tuyen finished playing two rounds
Any interest in this game?
When I'm a good person, the wolf wins
Why number 1, number 2, number 7
Obviously you guys are good people
But you keep talking like you're a bad person
You, when I protected you
I don't dare say it
My eyelashes keep flying up like this
I told you "I don't dare look at you"
Okay, after we've gone through two rounds of werewolves
recent special
We don't know the total achievements
So who knows?
Our brother Te Tu Quan knows
Why do you know?
So I am the village chief
The final results will now be announced to everyone
Based on rock, paper, scissors and werewolf
Summary of points accumulated from these two team games
Let's congratulate together
Ly Van Kiet and Ngao Khuyen
Joint first place
Congratulations you two
Lying down also wins
Is there any testament?
No, do you feel like you won?
In the immediate future it may be
If we have the chance, we will play a few more times
Is it possible to feel that pleasure?
That is, the joy after you fool everyone
Okay, congratulations you two will win
Collection of adorable enthusiastic teenage dolls
Sponsored by Mango
Congratulations you two
Congratulations
Now, we can open it up for everyone to see
So adorable
The joys of being in high school are simple
Singing, dancing
Ball, draw
Everyone remember Mango
Follow our collection of enthusiastic teen dolls
So our inference this time
The quick-witted collective activity here comes to a perfect end
Believe that through today's team game
The relationship between our new and old cooperative members
will be even more united
We also hope for all of our cooperative members
The inference society can grow stronger and stronger
Generate great light
Le commune deduced to become the brightest star
among high school teenagers
Thank you again to all our cooperative members
Thank you
Welcome everyone
VIP manufacturing program
"The brother who overcomes all difficulties"
This program is run by the Mango app
exclusive broadcast
Today the position we are standing in
It's the high school youth radio station
I am the creator
Qi Sijun
My identity is truly diverse
Yes, introduce to everyone
Because there are so many classic shows
They all came out from my hand
For example, "I did very well abroad" by Mr. Ly Thua Huyen
and Mr. Ly Thu Ham worked before
Seeing the program list behind us
There are many special programs like that
All come from my pen
But today
I'm about to release it
a program that I worked hard to create, called
What
"Classmates, please listen carefully"
We have to choose an editor for this program
So I chose three musical teenagers
in many applications sent back
Let's take a look at the three of them
After all, who can become an editor today?
Let us invite 3 editors to the floor
Please
Mr. Truong Ky
Mr. Cao Han Vu, Dai Ngu
Hello
We can make one
Make one
I don't use force
It turned out that the one who used the most strength was him
Three editors just came out
Has the atmosphere gotten a lot better?
It's been to the extreme
I introduced the three editors first
Here are the 4 people in front of you
They are devoted listeners of the radio station
our high school teenagers
Next here
We're about to get acquainted again
with three editors involved
competition session
Check out their materials list
What is the end result?
Which one comes first?
Let me go
Modeling
Come on, please
So handsome
Handsome photo
What is considered a "handsome photo"?
You're not handsome, are you?
People are also beautiful
Thank
Hello everyone, I am Cao Han Vu
Hay
Who is this guy?
Brothers, you watch
See this situation
Does it feel like you're normal?
Still pretty quiet?
Yes, you are extremely quiet
Is that right?
"American man" is quiet
Okay, let's introduce it
Of the sounds below, which ones can you represent?
I've saved it all
Mr. Cao Han Vu, I want to listen to this vibrant young man
That kind of extreme vitality
Okay
Mr. Au Duong Tinh, Mr. Truong Ky
Quick, go downstairs to get food
Today there is shredded pork
But very similar to the mermaid
After listening to this vital voice
I also want to listen to the domineering president
I want to see what the opposite feels like
Gao Han Yu, this is the new quarterly report
of our company over there
And also
Please check it out
First time reporting
So maybe me
There will probably be a few
Next time you talk, please keep your tongue straight
Our company doesn't need it
stammering person
If you can't do it next time
Then you don't need to go to work anymore
Sorry
This look
No need to go to work tomorrow
Who dares to work at his company?
Okay, show voice
No problem
Next here
How many letters and words can you say in 30 seconds?
What do you mean by marking X?
"X" is because I don't know either
Don't know yet
Represents infinite possibilities
Come on, that's what I said
OK, come on
Begin
30 seconds, I know
I really can't count how many words there are
When he spoke I didn't want to count anymore
Handed over to post-production
Continue
What can you do with your voice?
that others can't do?
Annoying "kills" people
Like this, I felt it just now
Thank you
Okay, sorry
Brothers, it's roughly like this
A bit of a fail
There is no such thing
Very good
Who is the next person?
Let me, me first
Next is Mr. Truong Ki
Hello everyone, I'm Truong Ky of the band Black Panther
First item
Mark an X for "gentle cooing voice"
Yes, this is not correct
Villainous voice
Or do we hear the villain's voice directly?
It sounds very bad, right?
Okay
Do you think what you say is correct?
Everything
Just let me arrange it
I have goosebumps already
Similar to the character type
in the game like that
Correct
This doesn't make sense
This is
How many words can you say in 30 seconds?
Because it's opera singing
A lot of times it is
One word can be sung for up to 20 seconds
Steam is also very long
Or today Mr. Truong Ky should try it a bit
Try one paragraph
Try a piece
So I sing a part
Final sound
The time is quite long
Understood
Warm up already
Mat
Door
Book
Top
At that time, I felt like I was
in the yard, in that place
Waving a fan
Same tea
Burn some incense
It will feel better
But it also shows the melody of opera
quintessence of the country
So good
Okay, next
You can use your voice to do it
What things can't others do?
Deep voice
How?
It's the current voice
Can you do that?
Looks like it can't be done
I almost choked
It's possible
You guys can
Let's try
Sing a verse
Whoever is shorter, okay?
You sing softly, right?
Comrade Tang Ham Giang
Where is spring?
It belongs to the type of distortion
Don't rush, take it slow
Voice a bit hoarse
Now, welcome our Mr. Truong Ky
Welcome
Next is Mr. Au Duong Tinh
Hello everyone, my name is Au Duong Tinh
Before introduction
I want to try
sing in that low voice
I have a way
Can sing lower than Truong Ky
Are you ready yet?
Ready
Where is spring?
Is it low?
It's too low
So what is it, who knows, let's get together
So now I go down to the 1st floor
Where is spring?
Alright
What's next?
Where to start?
What voice should you show first?
I want to explain a little
When filling out this list
I filled it in haphazardly
But
My filling in the situation is all done with sincerity
Because I fill out everything
I feel I can let Au Duong Tinh
Try each one
Is that Okay
Okay
So you have to explain a bit
The first one
Youthful voice
Young son
Boy
OK
Son's voice
I love you
That's a girl
Daughter, Mr. Au Duong Tinh
OK
Do it again
I love you
There is shyness in it
Okay, continue
What is that gentle, cooing voice?
Be spoiled
OK
Try it out
I love you
Alright, majesty of the king
Kingly
OK
Are you interested in playing my son?
Okay
Don't come over here
I feel
We have four children
really like it
But
I love you
This is the crown prince, right?
Crown Prince
Okay, next one
How many letters or words can you say in 30 seconds?
It's all just random writing
But there is sincerity
I can try
Try it out
Okay, a rapper that I like the most
I have a suggestion
Cut off my front part
Today's opening was truly amazing
So full of atmosphere, it's so great
So once again, welcome to the three of you
We also look forward to it
The three classmates have different styles
How will it be performed today?
The editing challenge has begun
Mr. Truong Ky has to go up
Mr. Cao Han Vu struggled persistently for a while
At this time, Mr. Au Duong Tinh
Mantises catch cicadas, sparrows lurk behind
The two colluded with each other
Next in the situation
don't know the item
Conduct PR
So I said it first, in my room
I like to use it the most
Today brings it to everyone
An extremely wonderful gift
When you eat, you will use it
You will use it when you sleep
How to use it while sleeping?
At bedtime
Next we show everyone
See this item
It's really extremely important
Mr. Truong Ki, I feel this
What is the most suitable gift for your brother?
in "The brother who overcomes all thorns" us?
Donate
Hey, try it on
Recreating him when he was 19 years old
This content is indeed worth paying to watch
So in the end, who can become?
editor today?